ibahn.com 2018-08-20

# GuestTek Privacy Policy

GuestTek Privacy Policy
GuestTek takes information security very seriously and attaches
great importance to the protection of your personal data. That's
why we respect your privacy and want you to be able to trust us
when it comes to data protection. We always inform you
transparently about what we need your data for and if and for how
long we store it. This allows you to decide for yourself for which purposes we may use your
data. To ensure the best possible security, the information is always transmitted to us in
encrypted form. If you no longer wish us to use your data, please let us know, for example by
email. GDPRinfo@guest‐tek.com
Content of this Privacy Policy
1. General Information
          1.1. Processing of Personal Data
          1.2. Controller
          1.3. Rights of the Data Subject
          1.4. Disclosure to Authority
2. Collection and Processing of Personal Data when visiting our Website
          2.1 Cookies
          2.2 Web Analytics
          2.3 Social Plug‐ins
          2.4 Social Login
          2.5 YouTube‐Videos
          2.6 Online Advertising
          2.7 Google Tag Manager
3. Objection or Withdrawal of your consent to the Processing of Personal Data
GENERAL INFORMATION
The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide you with information concerning the processing
of personal data when using our website and related services.
1.1. Processing of Personal Data
Personal data within the meaning of Art. 4 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation
(GDPR) are all information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, e.g. name,
address, email address, etc.
22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek             Page 1 of 7          Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

  1.2. Controller
  Responsible for the processing of personal data within the meaning of Art. 4 (7) GDPR is:
  GuestTek Interactive Entertainment Ltd.
  www.guesttek.com/contact‐us/
  e‐mail: GDPRinfo@guest‐tek.com
  1.3. Rights of the Data Subject
  As data subject affected by the data processing activity, you have the following rights with
  regard to your personal data according to Art. 15 et seqq. GDPR:
    Right of access;
    Right to rectification and to erasure;
    Right to restriction of processing;
    Right to data portability; and
    Right to object.
  Furthermore, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority concerning
  the processing of your personal data.
  1.4. Disclosure to Authority
  In the event of a legal obligation, we reserve the right to disclose information about you if we
  are required to surrender it to competent authorities or law enforcement bodies.
  COLLECTION & PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA WHEN VISITING OUR WEBSITE
  We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful bases.
  Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent), and “legitimate interests”.
  Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or
  decline your consent at any time and where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the
  right to object. If you have any questions about the lawful bases upon which we collect and
  use your personal data, please contact us GDPRinfo@Guest‐tek.com
  Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) b GDPR.
  What we collect
  We may collect the following information:
       o Name and job title,
       o Contact information including email address,
       o Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests,
       o Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
  22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek            Page 2 of 7            Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

  What we do with the information we gather
  We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
  and in particular for the following reasons:
       o Internal record keeping.
       o We may use the information to improve our products and services.
       o We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or
            other information, which we think you may find interesting using the email address
            which you have provided.
       o From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
            research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use
            the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  2.1 Cookies
  In addition to the aforementioned data, cookies and other similar storage technologies
  (hereinafter referred to as “Cookies”) are stored on your computer when visiting and using
  our website. Cookies are small text files that are stored by your browser on your device to
  save certain information. The next time you visit our website on the same device, the
  information saved in the cookies will subsequently be transmitted either to our website (“First
  Party Cookie”) or to another website to which the cookie belongs (“Third Party Cookie”).
  Through the information saved and returned, the respective website recognizes that you have
  already accessed and visited it with the browser you use on that device. We use this
  information to be able to design and display the website in an optimum way in line with your
  preferences. In that respect, only the cookie itself is identified on your device. Beyond this
  extent, your personal data will only be saved upon your express consent or if it is strictly
  necessary to be able to use the service offered to and accessed by you accordingly.
  This website uses the following types of cookies, the scope and functionality of which are
  explained below:
    Strictly necessary cookies (Type A)
    Functionality, Performance and Marketing Cookies (Type B)
    Consent based Cookies (Type C)
  You can find more information on the cookie types set and used in the description of the tools
  implemented on our websites in this privacy policy.
  2.1.1 Strictly necessary cookies (Type A)
  Strictly necessary cookies guarantee functions without which you cannot use our web pages
  as intended. These cookies are used exclusively by us and are therefore first party cookies.
  This means that all information stored in the cookies will be returned to our website.
  22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek            Page 3 of 7           Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

Strictly necessary cookies serve, for example, to ensure that you as a registered user always
remain logged in when accessing various subpages of our website and thus do not have to re‐
enter your login data every time you access a new page.
The use of strictly necessary cookies on our website is possible without your consent. For this
reason, strictly necessary cookies cannot be activated or deactivated individually. However,
you can deactivate cookies in your browser at any time (see below).
Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) b GDPR.
2.1.2 Functionality, Performance and Marketing Cookies (Type B)
Functionality cookies enable our website to store information already provided (such as
registered name or language selection) and to offer you improved and more personalized
functions based on this information. These cookies collect and store only anonymous
information so that they cannot track your movements on other websites.
Performance cookies collect information about how our websites are used in order to improve
their attractiveness, content and functionality. These cookies help us, for example, to
determine whether and which subpages of our website are visited and in which content users
are particularly interested. In particular, we record the number of visits to a page, the number
of subpages accessed, the time spent on our website, the order of the pages visited, which
search terms led you to us, the country, region and, if applicable, the city from which access
is made, and the proportion of mobile devices accessing our websites. We also capture
movement, clicks and scrolling with the computer mouse to understand which areas of our
website are of particular interest to users. As a result, we can tailor the content of our website
more specifically to the needs of our users and optimize our offering. The IP address of your
computer transmitted for technical reasons is automatically made anonymous and does not
allow us to draw any conclusions about the individual user.
You can adjust at any time the cookie settings (activate or deactivate) here.
2.1.3 Consent based Cookies (Type C)
Cookies, which are neither strictly necessary (Type A) nor functionality or performance cookies
(Type B) will be used only upon your express consent, e.g. marketing cookies.
We also reserve the right to use information that we have obtained by means of cookies from
an anonymous analysis of the usage behaviour of visitors to our website in order to display
specific advertising for certain of our products on our own websites. We believe that you as a
user benefit from this because we display advertising or content that we think suits your
interests based on your surfing behaviour, so that you will see less randomly scattered
advertising or certain content that might be of less interest to you.
22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek             Page 4 of 7            Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

Marketing cookies come from external advertising companies (third party cookies) and are
used to collect information about the websites visited by the user in order to create target
group‐oriented advertising for the user.
Opt‐out for cookies used for online advertising
You can also manage many companies’ cookies used for online advertising via the consumer
choice tools created under self‐regulation programs in many countries, such as the US‐
based https://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or                          the                           EU‐
based http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your‐ad‐choices.
You can withdraw your consent to the use of consent based cookies (Type C) individually at
any time with effect for the future by adjusting your cookie settings accordingly.
Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) a GDPR.
2.1.4 Administration and deletion of all cookies
You can set your web browser in such a way that cookies are generally prevented from being
saved to your device and/or that you are asked each time whether you are in agreement with
cookies being enabled. You can also at any time delete cookies that have been enabled again.
You can find out how all this works in detail from your browser’s help function.
Please note that generally deactivating cookies may lead to functional restrictions of our
website.
2.2 Web Analytics
GuestTek uses Google Analytics for our Web Analytics. For further information, please refer
to section 2.2.1 below.
2.2.1 Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google
Analytics uses a specific form of cookie, which is stored on your computer and enables an
analysis of your use of our website. The information about your use of this website generated
by the cookie is generally transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.
We would like to point out that Google Analytics has been expanded on this website to include
the code “gat._anonymizeIp();” to ensure the anonymized recording of IP addresses (so‐called
IP masking). Due to the IP anonymization on this website, your IP address is shortened by
Google within the territory of the EU and the Treaty States of the European Economic Area.
Only in exceptional cases the full IP address is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and
shortened there. Google has submitted itself to the EU‐US Privacy Shield,
(https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU‐US‐Framework).
22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek            Page 5 of 7           Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

Google uses this information on our behalf to analyze your use of this website in order to
compile reports on website activities and provide additional services related to website and
internet use. Google may also transfer this information to third parties as required by law or
if said third parties process this data on behalf of Google. The IP address transmitted by your
browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data.
You can prevent the storage of cookies by making the proper setting using your browser
software. In addition, you can prevent Google from recording the data related to your use of
the website generated by the cookie (including your IP address) and from processing this data
by         downloading           and     installing         the browser       plugin         available
at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
Third party information: Google Dublin, Google Ireland Ltd, Gordon House, Barrow Street,
Dublin 4, Ireland, Fax: +353 (1) 436 1001. Google Analytics Terms of
Service: https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html, General overview on Google
Analytics                            security                    and                            privacy
principles: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en as well as Google’s
privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en.
This website also uses Google Analytics for a device‐independent analysis of visitor flows,
which is carried out via a user ID. You can disable cross‐device tracking of your usage in your
Google Account under “My information”, “Personal information”.
Used Cookies: Type B. For further information, see 2.1
Cookie lifetime: up to 12 months (this applies only to cookies which have been set by this
website)
Maximum storage period of used data: up to 26 months.
Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) f GDPR.
3.1 Contacting
When contacting or communicating with us, e.g. by email or via contact form on our website,
the data you provide (your email address, if applicable your name and your telephone
number, or personal data submitted during the conversation) will be stored and processed by
us in order to answer your questions, requests or for the purpose of business related
correspondence. We delete the data arising in this context once storage is no longer
necessary, unless statutory retention obligations exist or periods of limitation must be
observed.
In case of consumer inquiries through our internal consumer management tool the personal
data will be usually deleted after one year.
22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek                 Page 6 of 7        Document Owner: SVP Technical Services

We transfer the collected data to the relevant internal departments for processing and to
other affiliated companies within the GuestTek Group or to external service providers,
contract processors (e.g. hosting, call center service providers) in accordance with the
purposes required (e.g. for establishing contacts, business related correspondence and
customer care).
Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) b GDPR.
3.2 Newsletter
The newsletter contains news, updates and further information on GuestTek. The newsletter
is distributed via email to a select group of customers. If you no longer wish to receive the
newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by replying “unsubscribe”.
These collected data are automatically deleted after 18 months if they no longer respond to
the newsletter, e.g. open (inactivity).
Legal basis: Art. 6 (1) a GDPR.
OBJECTION OR WITHDRAWAL OF YOUR CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA
If you have given your consent (Art. 6 (1) a GDPR) to the processing of your data, you can
withdraw your consent at any time. Such a withdrawal influences the permissibility of
processing your personal data after you have given it to us.
If we base the processing of your personal data on the weighing of interests (Art. 6 (1) f
GDPR), you may object to the processing. This is the case if processing is not necessary in
particular to fulfil a contract with you, which is described by us in the following description
of the functions. When exercising such objection, we ask you to explain the reasons why we
should not process your personal data as we have done. In the event of your justified
objection, we will examine the situation and either stop or adjust data processing or point
out to you our compelling reasons worthy of protection, on the basis of which we will
continue processing.
Of course, you can object to the processing of your personal data for purposes of advertising
and data analysis at any time. You can inform us about your objection under the above‐
mentioned contact details for the controller.
22.05.18 Privacy Policy GuestTek            Page 7 of 7          Document Owner: SVP Technical Services
